postaljobplacement.com 2016-04-14

# Privacy Statement | Postal Job Placement

#### POLICY

Postal Job Placement only contacts individuals who specifically request that we do so by providing their basic contact information.

Postal Job Placement collects information in two categories:

**Personally Identifiable Information (PII)**

We collect information from you when you register on our site. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

All such information is strictly protected and used only for delivering the content and products the user has signed up for or purchased. This information is NEVER used for other purposes and is NEVER shared with 3rd parties.

**Anonymous Usage History (non PII)**

This information is strictly limited to the history of activities that the user engaged in while on our site. it does NOT include any33 (PII).

For example, the string "sub+customer" in a cookie (see below for what cookies are) might indicate that you are both a subscriber AND a customer. The purpose of this information is to improve your experience.

For example, by storing the fact that you are already a subscriber, we do not need to bother you with an irrelevant subscriber box.

Similarly, by noting that you are a customer, we can "bookmark" the last video frames you watched in our member area and remind you of this the next time you visit.

There is a small subset of this history that we use with 3rd parties, such as Google, for the purpose of measuring and improving the efficacy of advertising campaigns.

Some of these third parties, aggregate such information across many websites. This allows them to identify users who are more likely to be interested in specific offerings like fashion, sports, education and so on.

As an Internet user, you may experience the results of such aggregation by noticing how the ads displayed on Yahoo, for example, better match your interests (the optimistic scenario), or at least more closely match a website that you recently visited.

Whether you find this annoying and spooky or helpful and relevant, or perhaps both, you are in good company. This area of Internet advertising is new and controversial. The tradeoff between privacy vs. commercial efficiency has a long history, for example the "Do not call" list.

In any event, it is likely that either the government or the industry will adopt some form of "opt out" capability in the future to address these concerns.

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions – Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, with out your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To send periodic emails – The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.
  * We may publicly identify you by first name only and location if you purchase our service.

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

Like many other commercial sites, our site utilizes standard technologies called "cookies" and clear GIFs to collect information about how our Site is used. We may use either of these to provide you with a more personalized experience.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small data text file, which a website stores on your computer's hard drive (if your web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to us. Cookies were designed to help a website recognize a user's browser as a previous visitor and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while the user was browsing the site.

A cookie cannot be read by a website other than the one that set the cookie. A cookie cannot pass on a computer virus or capture any of the Personally Identifiable information.

**Clear GIFs**

At times, we work with third-party service partners that employ clear GIFs (also known as pixel tags, single pixel GIFs, web beacons or action tags) for our benefit to help us measure advertising effectiveness.

Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of our users. The main difference between the two is that clear GIFs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.

Clear GIFs are not tied to your Personally Identifiable Information and only track the visitor traffic and behavior to and on our Site.

Clear GIFs can "work with" existing cookies on a computer if they are both from the same website or advertising company. That means, for example, that if a person visited "www.companyX.com", which uses an advertising company's clear GIF, the website would match the clear GIFs identifier and the advertising company's cookie ID number, to show the past online behavior for that computer. This collected information can be shared with the advertising company. We do, at times, provide such information to our third-party advertising service partners, but that information never includes personally identifiable information.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Your email information (email address, first name) is stored at the list server that delivers the Postal Job Placement free Postal Hiring Guide. Your information can only be accessed by those who help manage those lists in order to deliver e-mail to those who would like to receive Postal Job Placement products, services or free information.

All of the correspondence that is sent to you by Postal Job Placement include an unsubscribe link in them. You can remove yourself at any time from our newsletters by clicking on the unsubscribe link.

Postal Job Placement provides entry level job placement assistance to individuals seeking employment with the United States Postal Service. The Postal Job Placement Program is a service of Postal Job Placement, LLC, an independent agency dedicated to providing highly effective career preparation and development services and resources to job seekers throughout the United States. Postal Job Placement, LLC is not affiliated with or endorsed by the U.S. Postal Service, and does not guarantee the availability of any job, in any area, at any given time, nor can it guarantee any outcome of the postal hiring process. Postal Job Placement does, however, guarantee its program. If you do NOT pass the required postal exam, you are entitled to a full refund of your registration. The Postal Job Placement Program is optional, and is designed to assist postal job candidates throughout the entire postal job application, search, testing and interview process currently utilized for entry level jobs by the U.S. Postal Service.

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on 7/16/2011.

If you decide you no longer wish to receive communications from us you can easily opt out and or modify your account information by clicking on the Opt Out or Update links in the emails and correspondence you receive from us.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, please feel free to send us a brief message by using this form.
